{
    "file": "Task-3",
    "questionCount": 10,
    "notice": null,
    "questions": [
        {
            "index": 1,
            "question": "Who was the first Indian woman to win the Nobel Peace Prize ?",
            "answer": [
                "Indira Gandhi",
                "Kalpana Chawla",
                "Kiran Bedi",
                "Mother Teresa"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "index": 2,
            "question": "Who was the first woman of Indian origin to have reached space ?",
            "answer": [
                "Indira Gandhi",
                "Kalpana Chawla",
                "Sunita Williams",
                "Kalpana Chibb"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "index": 3,
            "question": "Who was the first female judge appointed to the Supereme Court of India ?",
            "answer": [
                "Sainya Sheikh",
                "Falima Akhtari",
                "Fathima Beevi",
                "Indira Banerjee"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "index": 4,
            "question": "Name the first Indian woman to be ranked Number 1 in WTA (World Tennis Association) double ranking .",
            "answer": [
                "Saniya Mirza",
                "Sucheta Kriplani",
                "Saina Nehwal",
                "P. V. Sindhu"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "index": 5,
            "question": "Which one of these ladies was the first female Governor of an Indian State ?",
            "answer": [
                "Sarojini Naidu",
                "Sucheta Kriplani",
                "Raj Kumari Amrit Kaur",
                "Vijay Laxmi Pandit"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "index": 6,
            "question": "First Indian woman to win Miss Earth title ?",
            "answer": [
                "Diya Mirza",
                "Reita Faria",
                "Zeenat Aman",
                "Nicole Faria"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "index": 7,
            "question": "First lady Chief Minister of an Indian State ?",
            "answer": [
                "Meira Kimar",
                "Indira Gandhi",
                "Annie Besant",
                "Sucheta Kriplani"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "index": 8,
            "question": "Who was the first woman to be awarded with the Bharat Ratna ?",
            "answer": [
                "Meira Kumar",
                "Indira Gandhi",
                "Sarojini Naidu",
                "Pupul Jayakar"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "index": 9,
            "question": "First Indian woman to win an Olympic Medal ?",
            "answer": [
                "Mary Kom",
                "Geeta Phogat",
                "Karnam Malleshwari",
                "Sakshi Mallik"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "index": 10,
            "question": "One of these four women belongs to the first batch of women to join the Indian Air Force in combat roles. Find her :",
            "answer": [
                "Tania Shergill",
                "Avani Chaturvedi",
                "Madhuri Kanitkar",
                "Priya Jhingan"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "index": 11,
            "question": "Something went Wrong! Oops",
            "answer": [],
            "correct": -1
        }
    ]
}